[{"answer": "You know, I never think of it that way, Piers.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 42, "question": "You are, as -- as I said at the top of this show, you are a kind of rock star, aren't you?", "qSentId": 41}, {"answer": "Well, we call it a service.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 59, "question": "What do you call it?", "qSentId": 58}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 102, "question": "Twenty-five minutes?", "qSentId": 101}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 104, "question": "So you have a 25 minute address which you memorize, right?", "qSentId": 103}, {"answer": "Well, I write -- I type what I'm going to say.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 107, "question": "Do you ever use notes?", "qSentId": 106}, {"answer": "You know, I don't know.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 127, "question": "Why have you emerged as the -- the big telegenic superstar do you think of this genre?", "qSentId": 126}, {"answer": "Well, I'm an optimist.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 134, "question": "What is the state of America spiritually right now, do you think?", "qSentId": 133}, {"answer": "You know, I see it both ways.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 147, "question": "What do you think is the reality?", "qSentId": 146}, {"answer": "I think in -- in one sense that we do need to change in -- like has been talked about a lot now -- to let go a little bit of the anger.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 179, "question": "Do you feel that America needs to change its direction?", "qSentId": 178}, {"answer": "It does.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 192, "question": "Something that's supposed to bring you hope and harmony and peace often has a completely direct affect, doesn't it?", "qSentId": 191}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 204, "question": "Do you try and calm people down?", "qSentId": 203}, {"answer": "You know, my encouragement would always be to obviously not use violence, to be peaceful.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 215, "question": "What do you do as a preacher of such influence?", "qSentId": 214}, {"answer": "Exactly.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 230, "question": "-- is the way you speak?", "qSentId": 229}, {"answer": "You know, I didn't -- I never -- I never got off into drugs.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 247, "question": "Were you allowed to be a naughty boy, Joel?", "qSentId": 246}, {"answer": "I never did.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 250, "question": "Never tried any of that stuff?", "qSentId": 249}, {"answer": "I never drank.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 253, "question": "Do you drink?", "qSentId": 252}, {"answer": "Still don't.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 256, "question": "You never drink alcohol?", "qSentId": 255}, {"answer": "Never had.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 258, "question": "Never had a drop?", "qSentId": 257}, {"answer": "I think, I --", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 261, "question": "Not even a tiny, little drop?", "qSentId": 260}, {"answer": "You know, one time we would --", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 263, "question": "Sneak in the back of the bike shed?", "qSentId": 262}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 265, "question": "When your dad wasn't looking, a little drop of cider?", "qSentId": 264}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 289, "question": "Do you drink?", "qSentId": 288}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 293, "question": "You -- you don't smoke?", "qSentId": 292}, {"answer": "No, don't take drugs.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 296, "question": "Never taken drugs?", "qSentId": 295}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 317, "question": "You know?", "qSentId": 316}, {"answer": "I think he instilled in me several.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 327, "question": "Well, what values did your father instill in you?", "qSentId": 326}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 347, "question": "Or do you believe that some people are simply born evil?", "qSentId": 346}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 354, "question": "Well, when you see someone like Adolf Hitler?", "qSentId": 353}, {"answer": "You know, I don't know.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 357, "question": "Was he born evil do you think?", "qSentId": 356}, {"answer": "You know, I may not right now.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 383, "question": "Do you -- you feel genuine forgiveness towards him?", "qSentId": 382}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 394, "question": "Right now, you find it hard to forgive him?", "qSentId": 393}, {"answer": "I think the greatest lesson -- well, I think probably the greatest lesson is just to be true to who you are, to follow your own heart.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 445, "question": "What was the greatest lesson he taught you?", "qSentId": 444}, {"answer": "Sure.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 455, "question": "Did he ever whack you?", "qSentId": 454}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 459, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 458}, {"answer": "We really didn't.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 464, "question": "Do you -- do you -- do you whack your kids?", "qSentId": 463}, {"answer": "Maybe a couple times.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 467, "question": "Never?", "qSentId": 466}, {"answer": "I'm the mean one --", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 471, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 470}, {"answer": "Well, I've really never seen it go.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 494, "question": "-- when does that fuse finally go?", "qSentId": 493}, {"answer": "Come on, Victoria.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 497, "question": "Isn't that unbelievable?", "qSentId": 496}, {"answer": "He must have a temper.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 499, "question": "Isn't that unbelievable?", "qSentId": 498}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 510, "question": "Like a fist fight?", "qSentId": 509}, {"answer": "Never have.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 514, "question": "Never?", "qSentId": 513}, {"answer": "Very competitive.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 521, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 520}, {"answer": "We are guilty.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 533, "question": "Guilty?", "qSentId": 532}, {"answer": "I think I've sold close to 20 million.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 546, "question": "How many books have you sold?", "qSentId": 545}, {"answer": "That's all the by product and all that stuff.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 549, "question": "Twenty million books?", "qSentId": 548}, {"answer": "Well, a lot of those too.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 552, "question": "DVDs?", "qSentId": 551}, {"answer": "I don't even know a figure.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 555, "question": "How many DVDs?", "qSentId": 554}, {"answer": "I never dwell on it.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 558, "question": "Do you know how much you're worth?", "qSentId": 557}, {"answer": "Well, again, I don't say that.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 579, "question": "Is it -- is there a contradiction there between saying, you know, \"God wants us all to be rich,\" if actually you're the only rich guy standing there?", "qSentId": 578}, {"answer": "I want you to be rich in health, in relationships.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 589, "question": "But do you want me to be rich?", "qSentId": 588}, {"answer": "You know, I don't know.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 594, "question": "How much do you think I should have?", "qSentId": 593}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 615, "question": "And what would you say, Victoria?", "qSentId": 614}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 629, "question": "Could you be happy and poor though, again?", "qSentId": 628}, {"answer": "I am so --", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 635, "question": "Do you not?", "qSentId": 634}, {"answer": "That's about it.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 643, "question": "Well, let's 20 million books, however many million DVD -- what other income do you have other than those?", "qSentId": 642}, {"answer": "It's been a lot.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 647, "question": "And we're talking like tens of millions of dollars, right?", "qSentId": 646}, {"answer": "I don't ever feel guilty because it comes from -- it's God's blessings on my life.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 650, "question": "Do you ever feel guilty?", "qSentId": 649}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 658, "question": "And you don't get paid by the church, do you?", "qSentId": 657}, {"answer": "Oh, yes.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 668, "question": "You know that?", "qSentId": 667}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 670, "question": "You've seen the criticism?", "qSentId": 669}, {"answer": "Well, that's my whole thing.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 680, "question": "-- what is wrong with being a prosperity preacher?", "qSentId": 679}, {"answer": "Oh, our church has raised millions and tens and -- you know, I don't even --", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 700, "question": "Do you know?", "qSentId": 699}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 702, "question": "Do -- do you know how much?", "qSentId": 701}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 711, "question": "Have you?", "qSentId": 710}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 724, "question": "Which obviously I don't think either of you two were born into great wealth, right?", "qSentId": 723}, {"answer": "Yes, I've always believed, Piers, the scripture shows that it's a sin.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 749, "question": "Is homosexuality a sin, in your eyes?", "qSentId": 748}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 760, "question": "Say, \"Come on, really upset your mother and dad here,\" you know?", "qSentId": 759}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 774, "question": "The song is on guitar?", "qSentId": 773}, {"answer": "You know, I'm so proud.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 776, "question": "What do you -- what do you feel when you watch that?", "qSentId": 775}, {"answer": "You know --", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 791, "question": "Which celebrities do you think are good role models?", "qSentId": 790}, {"answer": "Yes, she does.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 798, "question": "Taylor Swift?", "qSentId": 797}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 819, "question": "What is your -- is homosexuality a sin in your eyes?", "qSentId": 818}, {"answer": "Well, yes.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 844, "question": "So when you see civil partnerships being sanctioned, you think that's wrong, presumably?", "qSentId": 843}, {"answer": "Well, it's strictly back to what the scripture says.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 859, "question": "But why are they sinners in your eyes?", "qSentId": 858}, {"answer": "-- man, I would say \"I love you, Elton John.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 880, "question": "What would you say to him?", "qSentId": 879}, {"answer": "Well, to me, I just -- I'm not -- I'm not the one to judge and say, you know, who's bad and who's good.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 895, "question": "Aren't you?", "qSentId": 894}, {"answer": "Well, I believe it's -- I don't know that I understand it all.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 908, "question": "What do you -- how do they change -- what do they have to do to change to be better people?", "qSentId": 907}, {"answer": "I had not had a formal date.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 944, "question": "Joel, is it true that you have never had a single date with a woman, or anybody for that matter, until you met Victoria?", "qSentId": 943}, {"answer": "I was busy playing sports.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 950, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 949}, {"answer": "I was about 22.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 952, "question": "How old were you when you met Victoria?", "qSentId": 951}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 954, "question": "ORGAN: So 22 and never been kissed?", "qSentId": 953}, {"answer": "I had opportunity to break him in right.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 961, "question": "Victoria?", "qSentId": 960}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 963, "question": "Had you -- had you had boyfriends before?", "qSentId": 962}, {"answer": "It was.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 970, "question": "So both of -- both of you -- this was the first serious relationship?", "qSentId": 969}, {"answer": "I tell people for me it was.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 974, "question": "Was it -- was it love at first sight?", "qSentId": 973}, {"answer": "Well, he wasn't a preacher.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 992, "question": "I mean, they have to be pretty strict, right?", "qSentId": 991}, {"answer": "Well, we -- we --", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 1003, "question": "That's \"Son of a Preacher Man,\" isn't it?", "qSentId": 1002}, {"answer": "I don't know what that means.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 1005, "question": "Were you very chivalrous?", "qSentId": 1004}, {"answer": "I know there's --", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 1016, "question": "But are there any annoying aspects to Joel that we should be aware of?", "qSentId": 1015}, {"answer": "I'm probably way more spontaneous than he is.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 1020, "question": "-- what -- what annoys you about him?", "qSentId": 1019}, {"answer": "That was -- that was when I was a lot younger.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 1034, "question": "Have you been drinking today?", "qSentId": 1033}, {"answer": "I cracked up.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 1048, "question": "But when you heard him say that, what was your reaction?", "qSentId": 1047}, {"answer": "I thought it was funny.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 1050, "question": "Did you?", "qSentId": 1049}, {"answer": "Outside of marriage and children, outside of knowing the Lord -- coming to -- coming to know the Lord.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 1069, "question": "What's been the single greatest moment of your life outside of marriage and children?", "qSentId": 1068}, {"answer": "You know, I think it was an amazing moment when we opened up our new facility, the Compaq Center, where we took the church where my parents had had it for 40 years, and we moved into that premier facility there.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 1071, "question": "The -- the moment you'd like to relive again if you had the chance?", "qSentId": 1070}, {"answer": "He would be proud.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 1081, "question": "What would your dad have made of that you think at the moment?", "qSentId": 1080}, {"answer": "I do even better.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 1102, "question": "Will you feel the same way about meeting me, do you think, Joel?", "qSentId": 1101}, {"answer": "Lady Gaga.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 1111, "question": "Madonna or Lady Gaga?", "qSentId": 1110}, {"answer": "Oh, not --", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 1130, "question": "How on Earth have you connected to Lady Gaga?", "qSentId": 1129}, {"answer": "Oh, I think he's an angel.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 1138, "question": "Simon Cowell -- angel or the devil?", "qSentId": 1137}, {"answer": "I think -- I think he's -- I think he's smart.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 1142, "question": "What?", "qSentId": 1141}, {"answer": "Oh, yes.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 1144, "question": "You both think he's an angel?", "qSentId": 1143}, {"answer": "Oh, I --", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 1153, "question": "Justin Bieber, cute or annoying?", "qSentId": 1152}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 1165, "question": "Is the death penalty ever justified, and if so, when?", "qSentId": 1164}, {"answer": "If Osama Bin Laden was captured tomorrow --", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 1168, "question": "I struggle with that, you know?", "qSentId": 1167}, {"answer": "I think that it would probably be a good idea, you know, because of the people they hurt.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 1171, "question": "-- should he be executed?", "qSentId": 1170}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 1173, "question": "So execute him?", "qSentId": 1172}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 1175, "question": "Did Michael Vick deserve his second chance?", "qSentId": 1174}, {"answer": "I think everybody does.", "docId": "110126pmt", "aSentId": 1177, "question": "Do you think everybody does?", "qSentId": 1176}]